A Guide to the University of Virginia, Vice-President for Student Affairs, Committee Files 1958-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia, Vice-President for Student Affairs, Committee Files 1953-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/1/1.851
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content
University of Virginia, Vice-President for Student Affairs, Committee Files
Contents List
- Ad hoc Committee on Resident Assistant Qualifications (Hancock Problem), 1976, 1978 (Folder 1)
- Ad hoc Committee on Student Rights and Responsibilities (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Folder 1)
- Association of Residential Council (ARC), 1975-1976 (Folder 1)
- Board of Visitors Committee on Publications (Permanent Folder), 1958-1960 (Folder 1)
- Career Planning and Placement- Special, 1981-1983 (Folder 1)
- Cavalier Daily Press, 1975-1978 (Folder 1)
- Du Pont Regional Scholarships, 1970-1978 (Folder 2)
- Easley (Ken), 1976-1979 (Folder 2)
- Gay Student Union- 1976 Appeal, 1976-1979 (Folder 2)
- Gay Student Union vs. Board of Visitors (folder 1 of 3), 1972-1976 (Folder 2)
- Gay Student Union vs. Board of Visistors (folders 2 and 3 of 3), 1972-1976 (Folder 3)
- Honor Committee- Conference on Student Conduct, 1975 (Folder 3)
- Martin Luther King Memorial Fellowship Fund, 1968-1971 (Folder 3)
- Learning Enrichment Program 1973-1974, 1972-1980 (Folder 3)
- Scholarship Committee- Minutes of Meetings, 1968-1980 (Folder 3)
- VA PIRG (Virginia Public Interest Group), 1975-1977 (Folder 3)
- Young Americans for Freedom, 1977-1979 (Folder 3)